{"introPage":{"showIntroPage":false,"startButtonText":"Start Quiz","introduction":""},"progressType":"dots","passPercentage":50,"disableBackwardsNavigation":false,"randomQuestions":true,"endGame":{"showResultPage":true,"showSolutionButton":true,"showRetryButton":true,"noResultMessage":"Finished","message":"Your result:","overallFeedback":[{"from":0,"to":100}],"solutionButtonText":"Show solution","retryButtonText":"Retry","finishButtonText":"Finish","showAnimations":false,"skippable":false,"skipButtonText":"Skip video"},"override":{"checkButton":true},"texts":{"prevButton":"Previous question","nextButton":"Next question","finishButton":"Finish","textualProgress":"Question: @current of @total questions","jumpToQuestion":"Question %d of %total","questionLabel":"Question","readSpeakerProgress":"Question @current of @total","unansweredText":"Unanswered","answeredText":"Answered","currentQuestionText":"Current question"},"questions":[{"params":{}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"What is a leg in Polymesh?","answers":[{"text":"Transactions are bi-pedal and use their legs to move about.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Transaction processing is a journey, subdivided into stages, or legs.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"A portion, or step, of an instruction.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"Which of the following is a valid leg description?","answers":[{"text":"Alice sends 100 ACME shares from her trading portfolio to Bob's default portfolio.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Alice swaps 100 ACME shares for 100 US dollar tokens.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Alice offers 100 ACME shares at 1 US dollar per share.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"How is double-booking in another instruction's leg be avoided?","answers":[{"text":"New instructions can be created only after previous instructions have been settled.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"An asset's relevant quantity is committed when the owner affirms a leg.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Assets are frozen while pending instructions exist.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Double-booking is not a concern because affirmed instructions can still fail.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"Thinking of Polymesh's instructions as multiparty transactions, which of these statements are true?","answers":[{"text":"Instructions are settled after a majority of the parties agree that it's the right thing to do.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Multiparty transactions are not necessary because everyone acts independently.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"An instruction cannot be created without legs, and legs cannot be created outside of instructions.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"After it has been created, an instruction cannot be modified.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"Why can an instruction stay in a pending status after it is affirmed by all parties?","answers":[{"text":"The instruction will remain in a pending state until ACME's compliance rules are satisfied.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Network consensus will determine if the transaction is allowable.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"The transaction will not proceed without regulatory approval.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"All parties must also be in good standing with the validators.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"What is an atomic execution?","answers":[{"text":"That the instructions are always either completely executed or not executed at all.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"There is no case or interval when a transaction is partially executed.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"The cryptography is designed to repel theorised quantum computer attacks.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"The system will operate for 100 years between recharges.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Any small part of the instruction can execute, independent of the others.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"Which of these attributes of a custodial relationship are true?","answers":[{"text":"A custodian doesn't own the securities on-chain, the beneficiary still does.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"A custodial relationship can not be revoked.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Custodial transfers are semi-privat and surveillance resistent.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Custodians appear as owners on the chain. They are bound to clients by traditional legal structures.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"Does a venue creator control the accounts allowed to affirm instructions in its venue?","answers":[{"text":"False","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"True","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"What is a pre-authorisation in Polymesh?","answers":[{"text":"A signature that validates at least one future instruction.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"A signature that validates any number of future instructions.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"A signature that validates exactly one future instruction.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"There are no pre-authorisations.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"What are benefits of separating assets into logical portfolios within a single account?","answers":[{"text":"Assets across portfolios can have different balances while being connected to the same account.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Permissions can be delegated by portfolio.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Custody can be granted by portfolio.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Asset partitioning into logical portfolios facilitates good asset management.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}},{"library":"H5P.MultiChoice 1.14","params":{"question":"What does beneficial ownership mean in Polymesh?","answers":[{"text":"The benefits of ownership can be severed from actual ownership and traded separately.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"Beneficial ownership is always held by the beneficiary's account and is the base criteria to participate in corporate actions.","correct":true,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"There is no beneficial ownership. There is only ownership.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}},{"text":"It's like regular ownership, but with benefits.","correct":false,"tipsAndFeedback":{}}],"behaviour":{"singleAnswer":true}}}]}